Clement F. Haynsworth Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Clement F. Haynsworth Papers 1886-1989 (bulk 1957-1989)
MSS79781
Haynsworth, Clement F. (Clement Furman), 1912-1989
71,575 items
205 containers
81.8 linear feet
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Lawyer and judge. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, opinions, orders, briefs, writs, petitions, notes, agenda and minutes of meetings, and genealogical and printed material chiefly from Haynsworth's career as a federal judge on the United States Court of Appeals for the Fourth Circuit.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Barzun, Jacques, 1907-2012--Correspondence.; Brennan, William J., 1906-1997--Correspondence.; Burger, Warren E., 1907-1995--Correspondence.; Clark, Tom C. (Tom Campbell), 1899-1977--Correspondence.; Frank, John P. (John Paul), 1917-2002--Correspondence.; Haynsworth, Clement F. (Clement Furman), Jr., 1912-1989.; Hollings, Ernest F., 1922-2019--Correspondence.; Kennedy, Edward M. (Edward Moore), 1932-2009--Correspondence.; Lewis, J. Woodrow--Correspondence.; Meador, Daniel John--Correspondence.; Miller, Arthur R. (Arthur Raphael), 1934- --Correspondence.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994--Correspondence.; Powell, Lewis F., Jr., 1907-1998--Correspondence.; Thurmond, Strom, 1902-2003--Correspondence.; Walters, Johnnie M. (Johnnie McKeiver), 1919-2014--Correspondence.; Ward, Bernard J., 1925-1982--Correspondence.; Wright, Charles Alan--Correspondence.
Organizations
United States. Court of Appeals (4th Circuit)
Subjects
Administrative law--United States.; Antitrust law--United States.; Appellate courts.; Civil rights--United States.; Constitutional law--United States.; Industrial relations--United States.; Judges--United States.; Judicial opinions--United States.; Maritime law--United States.; Prisoners--Legal status, laws, etc.
Occupations
Judges.
Provenance
The papers of Clement F. Haynsworth, lawyer and judge, were received by the Library of Congress from the Haynsworth estate in 1990.
Additional Guides
A description of the Haynsworth Papers appears in Library of Congress Acquisitions: Manuscript Division, 1990, pp. 25-30.
Transfers
Sound recordings have been transferred to the Library's Motion Picture, Broadcasting, and Record Sound Division where they are identified as part of these papers.
Related Material
Papers related to Haynsworth's unsuccessful nomination to the United States Supreme Court are in the possession of Furman University located near Greenville, South Carolina.
Biographical Note
Date Event
1912, Oct. 30 Born, Greenville, S.C.
1933 A.B., Furman University, Greenville, S.C.
1936 LL.B., Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
1936 1957 Lawyer, Haynsworth, Perry, Bryant, Marion & Johnstone, Greenville, S.C.
1942 1945 Officer, United States Naval Reserve
1946 Married Dorothy Merry Barkley
1950 1951 Alternate member, Regional Wage Stabilization Board
1957 1989 Judge, United States Court of Appeals for the Fourth Circuit; chief judge, 1964-1981; senior judge, 1981-1989
1965 1981 Member, United States Judicial Conference; Executive Committee member, 1970-1981; Bicentennial Committee co-chairman, 1975-1981
1969 Nominated, United States Supreme Court
1989, Nov. 22 Died, Greenville, S.C.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of Clement F. Haynsworth (1912-1989), span the years 1886-1989, with the majority of the papers concentrated from 1957 through 1989 when Haynsworth was a judge on the United States Court of Appeals for the Fourth Circuit. The papers consist of three series: Personal Correspondence, United States Court of Appeals File, and Miscellany. There are no materials documenting Haynsworth's early life, his military service, or his career as a lawyer. Papers related to Haynsworth's unsuccessful nomination to the United States Supreme Court are in the possession of Furman University located near Greenville, South Carolina.
The Personal Correspondence series includes incoming and outgoing correspondence relating to Haynsworth's personal interests and activities. Because many of Haynsworth's friends were members of the legal profession, some of these letters also relate to his professional activities. Interfiled throughout this series are a few letters of his wife, Dorothy Barkley Haynsworth. There is little personal correspondence prior to 1976.
The United States Court of Appeals File constitutes almost all of the collection. This series documents Haynsworth's more than thirty years of service on the fourth circuit (Maryland, Virginia, West Virginia, North Carolina, and South Carolina). The papers are divided into three subseries: General Correspondence, Case File, and Office File. The General Correspondence subseries contains incoming and outgoing correspondence mainly from members of the legal profession and prisoners. The letters pertain primarily to fourth circuit administrative matters and contain complaints and pleas for legal assistance from prisoners. The "Congratulatory Correspondence" folder includes many letters to prominent members of the legal profession and government officials; a few of these letters contain comments by Haynsworth about his unsuccessful nomination to the Supreme Court. Other than the congratulatory correspondence, there is no correspondence prior to 1978.
The Case File subseries includes correspondence and memoranda, chiefly between judges, court clerks, and lawyers; opinions (drafts and printed copies); orders; briefs; writs; petitions; notes; background information; clippings; and printed matter. Many of the files also contain a sheet (photocopied from the outside of the original file folders during processing) that lists the judges on the panel, their votes (concurrences or dissents), and the concurrences or dissents of non-panel judges who reviewed the opinion. Cases are arranged chronologically by court term, October through June, and therein by case number. Opinions generated after June are filed in the previous October court term, e.g., an opinion written in August 1979 would be filed in the October 1978 term.
The majority of the case files pertain to civil cases and cases involving prisoner appeals and complaints. The files reflect the wide range of cases heard by the fourth circuit court on issues such as civil rights, constitutional law, labor relations, antitrust matters, maritime law, government regulations, and prisoners' rights. Many of the files for the terms from 1961 through 1967 contain only printed opinions; the Library did not receive any other material relating to these cases.
Also included in this subseries are cases documenting Haynsworth's occasional sittings on special three-judge district court cases (usually involving constitutional challenges to state statutes) and his service as a visiting judge for other circuits. These cases are filed at the end of the Case File subseries.
The Office File subseries relates to Haynsworth's administrative duties and professional activities during his tenure on the court of appeals. The files reflect his participation in judicial conferences and councils, admission ceremonies, legal organizations, and moot courts. Also documented are his interests in judicial conduct standards and in the creation of a national court of appeals that would reduce the Supreme Court's work load by hearing less important cases. An item worthy of note in this subseries is a thirty-six page document entitled "United States Court of Appeals for the Fourth Circuit," which provides a detailed description of the inner workings of the court (See the "General" file in container 166).
The final series in the papers, Miscellany includes correspondence, memoranda, reports, speeches, writings, photographs, genealogical material, and printed matter. The bulk of the series dates from 1957 to 1989 and relates to Haynsworth activities as an alumnus and member of the Advisory Council of Furman University.
The most significant and frequent of Haynsworth's correspondents are Jacques Barzun, William J. Brennan, Warren E. Burger, Tom C. Clark, John Paul Frank, Ernest F. Hollings, Edward Moore Kennedy, J. Woodrow Lewis, Daniel John Meador, Arthur R. Miller, Richard M. Nixon, Lewis F. Powell, Jr., Strom Thurmond, Johnnie McKeiver Walters, Bernard J. Ward, and Charles Alan Wright.
Organization of the Papers
The collection is arranged in three series:
Personal Correspondence, 1960-1989
United States Court of Appeals File, 1955-1989
Miscellany, 1886-1989
Container List
- Personal Correspondence, 1960-1989 (Box 1-6)
  Correspondence with friends, acquaintances, family, colleagues, and the public, including attachments and enclosures such as clippings and printed matter.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1960, Dec.-1977, June, (12 folders) (Box 1)
  - 1977, July-1978, Nov., (10 folders) (Box 2)
  - 1978, Dec.-1981, Dec., (10 folders) (Box 3)
  - 1982, Feb.-1985, Apr., (11 folders) (Box 4)
  - 1985, May-1989, Apr., (13 folders) (Box 5)
  - 1989, May-Nov., undated, (5 folders) (Box 6)
- United States Court of Appeals File, 1955-1989 (Box 6-201)
  - General Correspondence, 1959-1989 (Box 6-7)
    Correspondence and memoranda, including attachments and enclosures, between Haynsworth and judges, lawyers, court staff, prisoners, and the public relating to judicial matters.
    - 1978-1986, (7 folders) (Box 6)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 7)
    - Congratulatory correspondence, 1959-1975
  - Case File, 1956-1989 (Box 7-159)
    Correspondence, memoranda, opinions, orders, briefs, writs, petitions, notes, clippings and printed matter.
    Arranged chronologically by court term and therein by case number.
    - 1956 October term (Box 7)
      - J. M. Turner and Co. v. Commissioner, No. 7365
      - Long Mfg. Co. v. Holliday, No. 7383
      - Otto v. Koppers Co., No. 7401
      - Laseter v. Pet Dairy Prods. Co., No. 7403
      - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line R.R. v. Brotherhood of R.R. Trainmen, Lodge No. 514, No. 7416
      - Fralin v. Aronovitch, No. 7419
      - National Discount Corp. v. Tyson, No. 7434
    - 1957 October term
      - Fisher v. United States Life Ins., No. 7400
      - Wilkins v. Inland Mut. Ins. Co., No. 7445
      - Merck & Co. v. Olin Mathieson Chem. Co., No. 7473
      - Commissioner v. Peurifoy, No. 7479
      - Ross Coal Co. v. Cole, No. 7484
      - Dixon v. Virginian Ry. Co., No. 7493
      - Hardigg v. Inglett, No. 7508
      - New York Cent. R.R. v. Carr, No. 7519
      - United States v. Seaboard Air Line R.R., No. 7534
      - United States v. McIntyre, No. 7535
      - Mullen v. Winn-Dixie Stores, No. 7554
      - Ferguson v. Commissioner, No. 7558
      - United States v. One 1956 Ford Tudor sedan, No. 7564 (Box 8)
      - Atlantic Coast Line R.R. v. Boartfield, No. 7575
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Cranston Print Works Co., No. 7576
      - Leasure v. United States, No. 7583
      - Grady v. Irvine, No. 7584
      - Virginia Excelsior Mills v. Federal Trade Comm'n, No. 7590
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Local Union No. 9, Wood, Wire & Metal Lathers Int'l Union, No. 7594
      - Bradley v. Smyth, No. 7595
      - F. S. Bowen Elec. Co. v. United States Fidelity and Guar. Co., No. 7598
      - Kay v. United States, No. 7599
      - Selby-Battersby and Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 7600
      - John Hancock Mut. Life Ins. Co. v. Bennett, No. 7614
      - Morris v. United States, No. 7618
      - United States v. Durham Lumber Co., No. 7619
      - Ford Motor Co. v. McDavid, No. 7624
      - Tzu v. Robertson, No. 7629
      - American Sur. Co. v. Canal Ins. Co., No. 7631
      - Caviness v. United States, No. 7636
      - Sackett v. White, No. 7662
    - 1958 October term
      - Bostick v. Smoot Sand and Gravel Corp., No. 7578
      - Lee Tel. Co. v. Commissioner, No. 7676
      - Plater v. Warden, Md. House of Correction, No. 7679
      - Butler v. United States, No. 7682
      - Baldwin v. United States, No. 7684
      - Carpenter v. United States, No. 7686
      - Carva Food Corp. v. Equitable Fire and Marine Ins. Co., No. 7690
      - Call v. United States, No. 7705
      - Faraco v. Commissioner, No. 7717 (Box 9)
      - Crosse & Blackwell Co. v. Federal Trade Comm'n, No. 7719
      - Freeman v. Swink, No. 7720
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Empire Mfg. Co., No. 7726
      - Coleman v. Smyth, No. 7729
      - Jackson v. Steiner, No. 7736
      - Cargo Carriers v. Richmond Steel Co., No. 7743
      - Newsom v. Smyth, No. 7747
      - Noland v. Commissioner, No. 7766
      - Manville Boiler Co. v. Columbia Boiler Co., No. 7768
      - Starks v. United States, No. 7779
      - Fletcher v. Bryan, No. 7782
      - Manaia v. Potomac Elec. Power Co., No. 7786
      - Westcott-Alexander, Inc. v. Dailey, No. 7788
      - Martin v. United States, No. 7793
      - Baltimore Gas and Elec. Co. v. United States Fidelity and Guar. Co., No. 7809
      - Cooper v. Commissioner, No. 7816
      - Cunningham v. United States, No. 7817
      - Kosa v. Hicks, No. 7824
      - Milton v. Pure Oil Co., No. 7827
      - Thomson v. United States, No. 7844
      - Crawley v. United States, No. 7862
      - Thompson v. United States, No. 7869
      - Glatt v. G. C. Murphy Co., No. 7880
      - Griffin v. United States, No. 7921
    - 1959 October term (Box 10)
      - Milanovich v. United States, No. 7825
      - Walker v. United States Gypsum Co., No. 7846
      - Stanback v. Commissioner, No. 7855
      - Simpson v. Thomas, No. 7883
      - Shull v. Commissioner, No. 7884
      - Cooner v. United States, No. 7887
      - Stout v. Commissioner, No. 7892
      - Jones v. School Bd. of Alexandria, No. 7897
      - Riddick v. State Capital Ins. Co., No. 7902
      - Ostrofsky v. United Steelworkers, Locals 2609 and 2610, No. 7905
      - Largent v. Lemley, No. 7911
      - Doggett v. Commissioner, No. 7915
      - Jones v. United States, No. 7926
      - Hellenic Lines, Ltd. v. Brown & Williamson Tobacco Corp., No. 7931
      - Arnold v. United States, No. 7934
      - Jones v. Smyth, No. 7939
      - Holmes v. United States, No. 7947
      - International Bhd. of Teamsters v. United States, No. 7953
      - United States v. Jeffcoat, No. 7955
      - Raybourne v. Gulf Atl. Towing Corp., No. 7961
      - United States v. Brown, No. 7965
      - Alvord v. Commissioner, No. 7984
      - Roper v. United States, No. 7986
      - United States v. Bond, No. 7987
      - Rogers v. Commissioner, No. 7991 (Box 11)
      - United States v. W. R. Bonsal Co., No. 7992
      - World Carriers v. Bright, No. 7996
      - Henry v. Greenville Airport Comm'n, No. 8009
      - Davis v. United States, No. 8031
      - Bryan v. Commissioner, No. 8032
      - Tidewater Dev. and Sales Corp. v. United States, No. 8039
      - Hill v. School Bd. of Norfolk, No. 8053
      - Stiers v. Martin, No. 8060
      - Utica Mut. Ins. Co. v. State Farm Mut. Auto. Ins. Co., No. 8064
      - Santorinakis v. S.S. Orpheus, No. 8068
      - Jones v. United States, No. 8069
      - Gardner v. Tugboat L. N. Danzler, No. 8088
      - Bolling v. Smyth, No. 8090
    - 1960 October term
      - Mountain State Steel Foundries v. Commissioner, No. 8059
      - Holmes v. United States, No. 8084
      - Glendale Mfg. Co. v. Local 520, Int'l Ladies Garment Workers' Union, No. 8089
      - Hall v. United States, No. 8095
      - Ward v. United States, No. 8102
      - Kent Mfg. Corp. v. Commissioner, No. 8105
      - Horton v. Blalock, No. 8114
      - Jennings v. United States, No. 8117
      - Grannis & Sloan, Inc. v. Renegotiation Bd., No. 8122
      - Judy v. Pepersack, No. 8125
      - Chavis v. E. I. du Pont de Nemours & Co., No. 8133 (Box 12)
      - Jordan v. Warden, Md. State Penitentiary, No. 8136
      - United States v. Freeman, No. 8151
      - National Found. v. First Nat'l Bank, No. 8160
      - United States v. Borda, No. 8163
      - Thomas v. Peerless Mattress Co., No. 8167
      - Byrd v. Steiner, No. 8170
      - Player v. Steiner, No. 8171
      - DeFoe v. Duhl, No. 8192
      - Estate of Snyder v. United States, No. 8199
      - South Carolina Natural Gas Co. v. Phillips, No. 8201
      - United States v. Brown, No. 8205
      - Pomponio v. Commissioner, No. 8212
      - United States v. Rogers, No. 8214
      - Markham v. City of Newport News, No. 8216
      - Hargrove v. Little Constr. Co., No. 8219
      - Milestone v. Green Tree Corp., No. 8220
      - Hood v. Board of Trustees, Sumter County School Dist. No. 2, No. 8221
      - General Constr. Co. v. Hering Realty Co., No. 8225
      - Bew v. United States, No. 8233
      - Honolulu Oil Corp. v. Shelby Poultry Co., No. 8237
      - George v. South Carolina, No. 8242
      - United States v. Woodland Terrace, No. 8244
      - Shull v. Commissioner, No. 8250
      - United States v. Ayscue, No. 8251
      - Snider v. Cunningham, No. 8267
      - Lewis v. Lowry, No. 8298
      - Green v. Skibs A/S Mandeville and A.S. Klaveness & Co., No. 8319
      - Maryland Jockey Club v. United States, No. 8323
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Marval Poultry Co., No. 8324
      - United States v. Martin, No. 8344
      - Jones v. Cunningham, No. 8356
    - 1961 October term
      - United States v. Roberts, No. 8227
      - United States v. Boyette, No. 8248
      - United States v. Haith, No. 8275
      - Taylor v. Commissioner, No. 8289
      - United States v. Village Corp., No. 8296
      - United States v. Jacobs, No. 8311
      - Mason v. Mathiasen Tanker Indus., No. 8312
      - Austin v. United States, No. 8317
      - Williams v. Mutual of Omaha, No. 8352
      - Gardner v. National Bulk Carriers, No. 8362
      - Deering Milliken, Inc. v. Johnston, No. 8375
      - Millikin v. Commissioner, No. 8445 (Box 13)
      - Power and Combustion v. Wilson, No. 8468
      - United States v. Chatham, No. 8469
      - United States v. Gantt, No. 8478
      - New Amsterdam Casualty Co. v. Waller, No. 8480
      - Sheppard v. Cornelius, No. 8486
      - United States v. White, No. 8488
      - Union Trust Co. v. Kansas City Life Ins. Co., No. 8490
      - Johnson v. Commissioner, No. 8508
      - Shealy v. Challenger Mfg. Co., No. 8510
      - Swift v. Southern Ry. Co., No. 8516
      - Miller v. East Ga. Motors, No. 8523
      - Piedmont Fed. Sav. & Loan Ass'n v. Hartford Accident & Indem. Co., No. 8526
      - Hellings v. Ives Funeral Home, No. 8529
      - Bolling v. Cunningham, No. 8575
      - Virginia Greenstone Co. v. United States, No. 8577
      - United States v. Moore-McCormack Lines, No. 8581
      - Heath v. Ribicoff, No. 8600
      - Snyder v. Ribicoff, No. 8601
      - United States v. Lee, No. 8615
      - Gholston v. Boles, No. 8619
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Carteret Towing Co., No. 8623
      - Dillard v. School Bd. of Charlottesville, No. 8638
    - 1962 October term
      - Davis v. North Carolina, No. 8453
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Wix Corp., No. 8549
      - United States v. Smith, No. 8569
      - Jeffers v. Whitley, No. 8593
      - Clarke Baridon, Inc. v. Merritt-Chapman & Scott Corp., No. 8605
      - Roberts v. Pegelow, No. 8606
      - Wirtz v. Highway Transp., No. 8616
      - United States v. Crawley, No. 8659
      - Community Counselling Serv. v. Reilly, No. 8683
      - Leesona Corp. v. Cotwool Mfg. Corp., No. 8684
      - Potter v. Carvel Stores, No. 8685
      - Rutland v. Sikes, No. 8686
      - United States v. Lewis, No. 8693
      - Dingess v. United States, No. 8696
      - Hill v. Diamond, No. 8699
      - Norris Mfg. Co. v. R. E. Darling Co., No. 8720
      - Brunson v. Board of Trustees of School Dist. 1, Clarendon County, No. 8727
      - Clokey v. United States Parole Bd., No. 8735
      - Small v. Williams, No. 8740
      - United States v. Roland, No. 8744
      - American Football League v. National Football League, No. 8780
      - Bradshaw v. Celebrezze, No. 8791
      - United States v. Davis, No. 8807
      - Atlantic Seaboard Corp. v. Van Sterkenburg, No. 8811
      - North Carolina Nat. Bank v. United States Casualty Co., No. 8812
      - Nickelson v. Davis, No. 8819
      - United States v. Campbell, No. 8821
      - Harris v. Norfolk S. Ry., No. 8831
      - Patrick v. United States, No. 8832
      - Griffin v. Board of Supervisors, Prince Edward County, No. 8837
      - Ransburg Electro-Coating Corp. v. Proctor Elec. Co., No. 8844
      - Duggins v. Colonial Stores, No. 8865
      - United States v. Young, No. 8879
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Inland Motor Corp., No. 8885
      - New Amsterdam Casualty Co. v. Waller, No. 8889
      - Schack v. Preston Trucking Co., No. 8922
      - Fischer v. United States, No. 8930
      - Allen v. Standard Crankshaft & Hydraulic Co., No. 8935
      - United States v. Chatham, No. 8936
      - United States v. Ross, No. 8942
      - Summers v. Watkins Motor Lines, No. 8945
      - Spanos v. United States, No. 8963
      - In re Petition of A & H Transp., No. 9017
      - Woodson v. Chamberlain, No. 9028
    - 1963 October term
      - United States v. Kendrick, No. 8752
      - Osborn v. Sinclair Ref. Co., No. 8798
      - United States v. Taylor, No. 8822
      - FMC Corp. v. City of Greensboro, No. 8859
      - Maryland v. Baltimore Transit Co., No. 8941
      - United States v. S.S. Soya Atlantic, No. 8947
      - United States v. Brooks, No. 9009
      - Gadsden v. Fripp, No. 9021
      - Wicker v. National Sur. Corp., No. 9024
      - Galis Elec. & Mach. Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 9029
      - Hardware Mut. Casualty Co. v. Jones, No. 9032
      - United States v. Clark, No. 9033
      - Aptitude Assocs. v. Commissioner, No. 9034
      - Morgan v. Commissioner, No. 9035
      - Collins v. Rivers, No. 9046
      - United States v. Ellicott, No. 9052
      - Eaton v. Grubbs, No. 9058
      - French v. Hillman, No. 9060
      - United States v. Shew, No. 9067
      - Taylor v. Pegelow, No. 9072
      - Fidelity-Baltimore Nat'l Bank v. United States, No. 9078
      - Technograph Printed Circuits v. Bendix Corp., No. 9085
      - Frady v. Celebrezze, No. 9092 (Box 14)
      - McCloskey v. Maryland, No. 9100
      - United States v. Crews, No. 9103
      - United States v. M/V Wuerttemberg, No. 9109
      - Flota Maritima Browning De Cuba v. M/V Ciudad de la Habana, No. 9127
      - Coral v. Gonse, No. 9139
      - Woodson v. Gilmer, No. 9142
      - Joy Mfg. Co. v. Brooks, No. 9144
      - Brown v. Pepersack, No. 9148
      - Evans v. Cunningham, No. 9152
      - Ruckle v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 9169
      - Utica Mut. Ins. Co. v. Travelers Ins. Co., No. 9192
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Community Motor Bus Co., No. 9196
      - Goforth v. Allstate Ins. Co., No. 9210
      - Baines v. City of Danville, No. 9212
      - Associated Stores v. Industrial Loan and Inv. Co., No. 9222
      - Tart v. Smith, No. 9231
      - United States v. Grisby, No. 9234
      - Gilliam v. School Bd. of Hopewell, No. 9258
      - Wirtz v. Chesapeake Bay Frosted Foods Corp., No. 9265
      - United States v. Monaco and Son, No. 9272
      - United States v. Magliano, No. 9273
      - Pettaway v. County School Bd. of Surry County, No. 9286
      - Todd v. Sandidge Constr. Co., No. 9299
      - Guilford Mortgage Co. v. Cunningham Brick Co., No. 9323
      - United States v. Shoaf, No. 9336
      - Thompson v. Commissioner, No. 9363
      - Katz v. Peyton, No. 9377
      - Kinsley v. Markovic, No. 9380
      - Switzerland Co. v. Udall, No. 9385
      - Blumenthal v. Commissioner, No. 9397
      - Gallegly v. White, No. 9416
      - Commissioner v. Offutt, No. 9427
      - James River Hydrate and Supply v. United States, No. 9433
      - Johnson v. Allstate Ins. Co., No. 9439